module.exports = {
    name: 'Quiz 1',
    type: 'multiple choice',
    problems: [
        {
            question: 'What does the red line on the curve mean?',
            a: 'No vehicle is allowed to park there',
            b: 'Vehicle is allowed to park there',
            c: 'Vehicle is allowed to path there but within a time limit',
            answer: 'No vehicle is allowed to park there'
        },
        {
            question: 'What is the residential speed limit?',
            a: '30mph',
            b: '25mph',
            c: '20mph',
            answer: '25mph'
        },
        {
            question: 'If an emergency vehicle behind you has sirens on, what do you do?',
            a: 'Enter the rightest lane of the road and stop',
            b: 'Enter the rightest lane of the road and continue driving',
            c: 'Continue driving',
            answer: 'Enter the rightest lane of the road and stop'
        },
        {
            question: 'If the police car is following with sirens, on you:',
            a: 'Annoy him (her)',
            b: 'Escape!',
            c: 'Pull over to the right and stop',
            answer: 'Pull over to the right and stop'
        },
        {
            question: 'What does the yellow light on the traffic light mean?',
            a: 'Stop immediately',
            b: 'Beat the light by increasing your speed',
            c: 'Proceed with caution',
            answer: 'Proceed with caution'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is one of the steps of changing lanes?',
            a: 'Turn on your signal',
            b: 'Look over your shoulder',
            c: 'All of the above',
            answer: 'All of the above'
        },
        {
            question: 'A minor cannot drive between what times?',
            a: 'Between 9pm to 6am',
            b: 'Between 11pm to 5am',
            c: 'Between 12pm to 7am',
            answer: 'Between 11pm to 5am'
        },
        {
            question: 'When do you yield other drivers?',
            a: 'Whenever you turn at an intersection',
            b: 'At an intersection without a stop sign facing you',
            c: 'All of the above',
            answer: 'Whenever you turn at an intersection'
        },
        {
            question: 'What are carpool lanes used for?',
            a: 'For vehicles with two or more occupants, motorcycles, and transits',
            b: 'For only emergency vehicles',
            c: 'For vehicles with only one occupant',
            answer: 'For vehicles with two or more occupants, motorcycles, and transits'
        },
        {
            question: 'Do you have the right of way when turning left against an unprotected left turn light?',
            a: 'Yes, you have the right of way.',
            b: 'No, you must yield right of way to drivers from the opposite side.',
            c: 'Never!',
            answer: 'No, you must yield right of way to drivers from the opposite side.'
        }
    ]
}

